

ABOUT ME

Highly motivated front-end developer with 2 years of experience

IT-sphere doesn't stand still, it has many challenges, opportunities,

there are interesting and at the same time complex tasks, which means that this is a platform for constant work on yourself and development. Eager to build long-term relationships with generationally impactful company.

EDUCATION

National Aviation University Technical information security systems

09.2013 - 01.2015

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JS, REACT, GIT.

Additional: Photoshop, Figma, Ads Manager, Little - Python and PHP

LANGUAGE

Ukrainian - Native Russian - Full

English - Intermediate

Dirksen Artem

Front-end Developer



WORK EXPERIENCE

Friend's Arbitration team Kyiv

06.2020 - 03.2022

Targetologist, creative manager

Full-cycle of Facebook advertise processes.

Making landing pages, creating video/photos creatives,

push advertise in facebook, tik-tok ads managers. Solving issues with getting response from 'post' form's and integration with crm.

OfferLeader Kyiv

02.2019 - 03.2020

Creative manager

Making landing pages, creating video/photos creatives,

push advertise in facebook, tik-tok ads managers. Solving issues with getting response from 'post' form's and integration with crm.

Freelancing on my own

05.2019 to today

Everything I can

Creating websites, making photo/video creatives.